Finding Aid for A. Alfred Taubman papers, 1942-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Topical 1957-2006
  - Organization/Subject 1967-2006
    - A-E and S-U 1972-1980
      - Cavanaugh, Jerry (Box 174)
      - Central Business District, City of Detroit (Box 174)
      - Chromalloy, Capital Avenue (Box 174)
      - Columbia Savings & Loan Assoc. (Box 174)
      - Committee for Economic Development (Box 174)
      - Common Area Maintained Budgets (Box 174)
      - Condominiums (Box 174)
      - Construction (Box 174)
      - Construction Status Reports (Box 174)
      - Cooper & Wiles (Box 174)
      - Corniche Convertible (Box 174)
      - Corporate Communications (Box 174)
      - Corporation Consolidation (Box 174)
      - The Corporate Director Letter (Box 174)
      - Courtesy Towing & Recovery Service, Inc. (Box 174)
      - The Edward J. De Bartolo Corporation (Box 174)
      - Democratic National Convention (Box 174)
      - Department Stores (Box 174)
      - The Detroit Club (Box 174)
      - Detroit Country Day School (Box 174)
      - Duffel, Joe (Box 174)
      - Dunhill of London (Box 174)
      - Earthquake Coverage (Box 174)
      - Eastern Michigan University (Box 174)
      - Eastern Shopping Centers, Inc. (Box 174)
      - Economic Club of Detroit (Box 174)
      - Economic Development Corporation of Greater Detroit (Box 174)
      - Economy (Box 175)
      - Employment (Box 175)
      - Energy (Box 175)
      - England (Box 175)
      - Environmental Comment (Box 175)
      - Environmental Protection (Box 175)
      - Environmental Protection Meeting (Box 175)
      - European Institutional Investor Conference (Box 175)
      - Evans & Hillman, Inc. Lighting Design (Box 175)
      - Frances Denney Corporation (Box 175)
      - Tom Spiegel Enterprises (Box 175)
      - State Mutual Investors (Box 175)
      - Stocker & Stitler (Box 175)
      - Teachers Insurance (Box 175)
      - Transamerica Pyramid (Box 175)
      - Transportation (Box 175)
      - U.S. Conference of Mayors (Box 175)
      - Urban Development (Box 175)
      - Urban Land Research Foundation (Box 175)
    - A-U 1966-1980
      - Alexander, Linn (Quintana) (Box 176)
      - Allen, Charles (Box 176)
      - Associated Dry Goods Corp. (Box 176)
      - Bart (Box 176)
      - Bendel, Henri (Box 176)
      - California Association for A.C.T. (Box 176)
      - Carter, Hawley, Hale (Box 176)
      - Chase Manhattan Bank (Box 176)
      - Citibank (Box 176)
      - Coldwell Banker (Box 176)
      - Columbia Pictures Industries, Inc. (Box 176)
      - Cummings, Peter D. (Box 176)
      - Cummings, Ruth (Box 176)
      - Damon Raike and Company (Box 176)
      - Dayton Hudson Properties (Box 176)
      - Detroit Institute of Arts (Box 176)
      - Detroit Symphony Orchestra (Box 176)
      - Dobbs, Leonard (Box 176)
      - Doner, W.B. & Company (Box 176)
      - Eastdil Realty, Inc. (Box 176)
      - Federal Trade Commission (Box 176)
      - Federated (Box 176)
      - Florsheim Shoes (Box 176)
      - Gantos (Box 176)
      - Genesco (Box 176)
      - Hahn, Ernest W., Inc. (Box 176)
      - Harvard (Box 176)
      - Herman's (Box 176)
      - Hilton (Box 176)
      - Himelhoch's (Box 176)
      - Hoffritz (Box 176)
      - Hudson, Jean, Wedding, Daughter of Joseph Hudson (Box 176)
      - Hughes & Hatcher (Box 176)
      - Hyatt Corporation (Box 176)
      - Ice Arenas (Box 176)
      - Interlochen Center for the Arts (Box 176)
      - Jacobsons (Box 176)
      - Japan (Box 176)
      - Javits, Senator (Box 176)
      - Kennedy Center (Box 176)
      - Kiplinger California Letter (Box 176)
      - Kogan, Jay M. (Box 176)
      - Kohl, Sidney, Lawsuit (Box 176)
      - Kresge, S. S. Company (Box 176)
      - Lang, George Corporation (Box 176)
      - Larson, Robert (Box 176)
      - Leasing Reports (Box 176)
      - Lerner Stores Corporation (Box 176)
      - Leventhal, Kenneth & Company (Box 176)
      - Liberty House (Box 176)
      - Limited Stores (Box 176)
      - Lord & Taylor (Box 176)
      - Lyon, Phillip (Box 176)
      - Magic Pan (Box 177)
      - Cyril Magnin (Box 177)
      - Joseph Magnin (Box 177)
      - Macy's (Box 177)
      - Mall Properties, Inc. (Box 177)
      - Malls (Box 177)
      - Manufacturer's Bank 1974-1979, 4 folders (Box 177)
      - May Department Stores (Box 177)
      - William G. Milliken (Box 177)
      - NACORE (Box 177)
      - Name-O-Graph (Box 177)
      - National Mall Monitor (Box 177)
      - Neiman Marcus (Box 177)
      - Newhall Land & Farming Co. (Box 177)
      - Olga's Kitchen (Box 177)
      - J.C. Penney 1972-1979 (Box 177)
      - Penn Central (Box 177)
      - Photographs/Malls (Box 177)
      - Prudential Insurance Co. (Box 177)
      - Racquet Club of Palm Springs (Box 177)
      - Republican National Convention (Box 177)
      - Restaurants (Box 177)
      - Riverfront (Box 177)
      - Arthur Rubloff & Co. (Box 177)
      - Saks Fifth Avenue (Box 177)
      - San Francisco Tennis Club (Box 177)
      - Sears Roebuck & Co. (Box 177)
      - Security Pacific National Bank (Box 177)
      - Southeast Michigan Transportation Authority (SEMTA) (Box 177)
      - Sinai Hospital (Box 177)
      - Sinai Hospital, "Sinai in the Press," 1978 (Box 177)
      - Sixty Minutes (Box 177)
      - Speeches 1967-1974, 6 folders (Box 177)
      - Speeches 1975-1979, 5 folders (Box 178)
      - Speeches, Miscellaneous (Box 178)
      - United Artists Theatre Circuit, Inc. (Box 178)
      - U.S. Shoe Corporation (Box 178)
      - U.S. Specialty Retailing, Inc. (Box 178)
    - A-U 1967-1994 (bulk 1979-1994)
      - Allegheny & Western Energy Corp. (Box 179)
      - Allen & Company (Box 179)
      - Allied Hambro (Box 179)
      - American Enterprise Institute (Box 179)
      - American Motors Corp. (Box 179)
      - American Natural Resources Co. (Box 179)
      - Associated Dry Goods Corporation (Box 179)
      - B. Altman & Co. (Box 179)
      - A.H. Belo Corp. (Box 179)
      - Bojangles (Box 179)
      - Bradford National (Box 179)
      - Bren Company (Box 179)
      - Burnham, Walling & Co. (Box 179)
      - Carter Hawley Hale Stores, Inc. (Box 179)
      - Castle & Cooke, Inc. (Box 179)
      - Cattle Branding (Box 179)
      - Coldwell Banker (Box 179)
      - Columbia Savings & Loan (Box 179)
      - Commercial Paper (Box 179)
      - Concordia-Argonaut (Box 179)
      - CORE Industries (Box 180)
      - Damon Raike & Co. (Box 180)
      - Davenport, Eugene (Box 180)
      - Development Choices for the 80s (Box 180)
      - Disney (Box 180)
      - W.B. Doner & Co. (Box 180)
      - Drexel Burnham Lambert (Box 180)
      - Enertech/Oil Mop, Inc. Stock (Box 180)
      - Fiduciary Responsibilities of the Trustee (Box 180)
      - Florsheim Retail Division (Box 180)
      - Fraser Shopping Center (Box 180)
      - Gantos (Box 180)
      - Gap Stores, Inc. (Box 180)
      - Garfinkel, Brooks Brothers, Miller & Rhoads, Inc. (Box 180)
      - General Health Services (Box 181)
      - Genesco (Box 181)
      - Getty Oil
        - Correspondence (Box 181)
        - General, 2 folders (Box 181)
        - Newspaper Clippings (Box 181)
        - Operating File (Box 181)
      - Green Timbers Tract (Box 181)
      - Ernest Hahn, Inc. (Box 181)
      - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich Stock (Box 181)
      - Sid Harris Racetracks (Box 181)
      - Hecht's (Box 181)
      - Heck's, Inc. (Box 181)
      - Helionetics (Box 181)
      - Hodges, Laurie, Florida Land Development (Box 181)
      - J.L. Hudson (Box 181)
      - Hughes & Hatcher Co. (Box 181)
      - Ice Rink files (Box 181)
      - Intermagnetics General Corp. (Box 181)
      - Lane Bryant (Box 181)
      - Longview Fibre Co. (Box 181)
      - Lord & Taylor (Box 181)
      - Marathon Oil Company (Box 181)
      - Marshall Field (Box 181)
      - Marx/Handley Productions (Box 181)
      - Massachusetts Institute of Technology (Box 181)
      - May Company (Box 181)
      - Metropolitan Fund (Box 181)
      - F.W. Meyers Company (Box 181)
      - National Golf Links (Box 182)
      - New York One (Box 182)
      - North Park Towers (Homac Barnes, Inc.) (Box 182)
      - Oceanic Exploration Company (Box 182)
      - Oil (Box 182)
      - Olin Foundation (Box 182)
      - Ontario Motor Speedway (Box 182)
      - Outlet Company (Box 182)
      - Pacific Bank (Box 182)
      - Pantry Pride, Inc. (Box 182)
      - T. J. Parrent, Inc. (Box 182)
      - J. C. Penney (Box 182)
      - Peralta Oaks Office Building (Box 182)
      - Petco (Box 182)
      - Petrie Stores (Box 182)
      - Public Television (Box 182)
      - Raleigh Square Marketplace (Box 182)
      - Randhurst (Mt. Prospect, IL) (Box 182)
      - Reliance Group, Inc. (Box 182)
      - Restaurant Leslie, Inc. (Box 182)
      - Ridge Bancorporation of Wisconsin (Box 182)
      - J. B. Robinson Jewelers (Box 182)
      - Rothschild Asset Management (Box 182)
      - Rouse Company (Box 182)
      - Rovac Corporation (Box 182)
      - Rovac Corporation, AAT personal (Box 182)
      - Arthur Rubloff & Co. (Box 182)
      - R. V. Limited (Robert Vance) (Box 182)
      - San Francisco Tennis Club (Box 182)
      - Savoy Hotels, London (Box 183)
      - Saxon Theatres (Box 183)
      - Sears (Box 183)
      - Shoppers Fair (Box 183)
      - Standard Oil Co. (Indiana) (Box 183)
      - Stephenson & Co. (Box 183)
      - Stoneson Development Corporation (Box 183)
      - Storer Broadcasting (Box 183)
      - Sunset Plaza Apartment, Florida (Box 183)
      - Tampa, City of (Box 183)
      - Techmart (Box 183)
      - Thimbles (Box 183)
      - Toch Brothers, Super Sol Ltd. Stock (Box 183)
      - TV Station (Box 183)
      - Tyner, Irving (Box 183)
      - United States Shoe Corporation (Box 183)
    - M-Y 1969-1994
      - Manufacturers Bank, Directors & Officers Questionnaires 1977-1985, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - Marguleas, Howard 1980-1989 (Box 184)
        (includes photograph)
      - Mark's Club 1984-1992 (Box 184)
      - Mason, Harry 1982-1988 (Box 184)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art 1985-1988 (Box 184)
      - Mewar (Maharana B.S. Mewar) 1984 (Box 184)
      - Michigan Business Partnership 1989-1993 (Box 184)
      - Michigan Development Foundation 1986-1991 (Box 184)
      - Michigan Partnership for New Education 1992, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - Miro Miro & Weiner 1982-1990, 2 folders (Box 184)
      - N Miscellaneous-1984-1991 (Box 184)
      - National Committee of U.S.-China Relations-1981-1990, 6 folders (Box 184)
      - National Employer Leadership Council 1994 (Box 185)
      - P Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 185)
      - Palm Beach Country Club 1977-1990 (Box 185)
      - Park Films-1986-1987 (Box 185)
      - Philanthropic Institute 1993 (Box 185)
      - Pips International Inc. 1984-1985 (Box 185)
      - Pontiac Silverdome 1972-1994 (Box 185)
      - Pritzker, Jay 1975-1980 (Box 185)
      - Q Miscellaneous 1986-1988 (Box 185)
      - R Miscellaneous 1984-1991 (Box 185)
      - Ronald Reagan (inauguration) 1987-1991 (Box 185)
      - Remembrance Day Lecture 1989 (Box 186)
      - Riverfront Projects, The Fisher Group 1993 (Box 186)
      - Rockefeller University (Box 186)
      - Salmon Project 1984-1989 (Box 186)
      - Scarab Club (Box 186)
      - Stroock and Stroock and Lavan (795 Fifth Avenue Corp.), 3 folders (Box 186)
      - Sinai Hospital 1980-1984 (Box 187)
      - 650 Madison Avenue 1984-1988 (Box 187)
      - Sloan Kettering Cancer Center 1986-1990 (Box 187)
      - Smithsonian Institute (Box 187)
      - Solomon Equities 1986-1990 (Box 187)
      - Southampton Association 1983-1994 (Box 187)
      - Southampton Hospital 1987-1994 (Box 187)
      - Southern Realty 1985-1991 (Box 187)
      - A. Alfred Taubman Speeches, undated 1980-1994, 8 folders (Box 188)
      - Speeches of Others (friends and associates), undated 1977-1994, 16 folders (Box 188)
        (also includes collected material to be used in speech preparation)
      - Spoleto 1986-1994 (Box 189)
      - State of Israel Bond 1959-1987 (Box 189)
      - Stocker & Sitler Inc.
        - General 1980-1987 (Box 189)
        - Oil & Gas 1979 (Box 189)
      - Sugar Babies Company 1979-1993 (Box 189)
      - T Miscellaneous 1985-1994 (Box 189)
      - Taubman Centers Inc./Taubman Board 1992-1994 (Box 189)
      - Taubman Company
        - AAT Associates 1978 (Box 189)
        - A.R.T. Properties (Box 189)
        - Accounting and Financial 1977-1980, 2 folders (Box 189)
        - Directors and Stockholders 1976-1978 (Box 189)
        - Directors Meetings 1976-1978 (Box 189)
      - Taubman Realty Group 1985-1993 (Box 190)
      - Taubman Theatres/Cineplex (1984 transaction) 1972-1988 (Box 190)
      - Teachers College Retirement Equities Fund 1987 (Box 190)
      - The "Thin Man Co" Ltd. 1991 (Box 190)
      - Trump Articles 1984 (Box 190)
      - Trump Towers (Box 190)
      - Tufo & Zucotti (Peter Tufo Residence) (Box 190)
      - Turns Company 1983-1984 (Box 190)
      - U Miscellaneous (Box 190)
      - USG Corporation 1991 (Box 190)
      - University Cultural Center Housing Development-Detroit, MI 1989-1991, 2 folders (Box 190)
      - University of Detroit 1985-1989, 2 folders (Box 190)
      - USIA 1988 (Box 190)
      - V Miscellaneous 1987-1993 (Box 190)
      - Voice Foundation 1982-1989 (Box 190)
      - Volunteer (organization) 1984-1995 (Box 190)
      - Von Matthiessen, Maria 1984 (Box 190)
      - Wexner Center/Ohio State University 1984-2006 (Box 191)
      - Wexner Land Development Drawing (Box 191)
      - Photographs of Wexner Property, August 1991 (Box 191)
      - Les Wexner's 50th Birthday 1987 (Box 191)
      - Trustee Meeting March 11, 2000, May 17, 2005 (Box 191)
      - Wexner Center for Visual Arts, Ohio State University, Indemnification Agreement-1986-1994 (Box 191)
      - White House Preservation Fund 1984-1990, 9 folders (Box 191)
      - Whitney Museum
        - Building File 1982, 1984-1986, 4 folders (Box 192)
        - General Correspondence 1987-1990 Meeting of October 12, 1990 (Box 192)
        - 1986-1987 Schemes, Capital Campaign Committee (Box 192)
        - Meeting Notes & Membership Roster 1985-1987 (Box 192)
        - Facilities Committee (Box 192)
        - Board of Trustees-1982-1985 (Box 192)
        - Building Program 1982 (Box 192)
        - Policy Statement/Contributions 1991-1994 (Box 192)
        - Trustees Handbook 1981 (Box 192)
        - Working Papers toward a Building Program 1982 (Box 192)
        - Board of Trustees Meeting February 19, 1992 (Box 192)
        - Preliminary Planning Study 1980 (Box 192)
        - Painting & Sculpture Committee 1984-1994 (Box 192)
        - Union Problems 1983-1984 (Box 192)
      - Robert C. Wilson, Ice-Fire/Crooked Tree (book & movie) 1984-1986 (Box 192)
      - YMCA (Pontiac) 1985 (Box 192)
      - Evelle Younger 1978 (Box 192)
    - A-Z 1975-2003
      - ARS Associates 1978 (Box 193)
      - Art in Public Places 1978 (Box 193)
      - Dennis Archer 1996-1997 (Box 193)
      - Athena Group 1993-2004, 5 folders (Box 193)
      - Athena Group, Manezhnaya Square, Moscow 1995-1996 (Box 193)
      - Briarwood 1978-1980 (Box 193)
      - Business Committee for the Arts 1994-1995 (Box 193)
      - Chase Manhattan Corporation
        - Correspondence 1986-1998 (Box 193)
        - Fee Deferral 1986-1991 (Box 193)
        - Lawsuit 1991-1993 (Box 193)
        - Proxy Information 1986-1995 (Box 193)
        - Proxy Information 1986-1995 (cont.) (Box 194)
        - Retirement Plan (Box 194)
      - Courtauld Institute 1995-1997 (Box 194)
      - Detroit Economic Growth Corporation 1987-1997 (Box 194)
      - Detroit Executive Services Corps 1991-1999 (Box 194)
      - Detroit Medical Center, Conflict of Interest Disclosures 1982-1993 (Box 194)
      - Detroit Renaissance Board of Directors 1972-1975, 1995-2002, 2 folders (Box 194)
      - E.A.R.T.H. College 1993-2000 (Box 194)
      - Ellis Island Medal of Honor 1995-1996 (Box 194)
      - Emmanuel College, England 1993-1995 (Box 194)
      - Fairfax Associates 1972-1981 (Box 194)
      - Fairlane Town Center 1979-1981 (Box 194)
      - Greater Washington Research Center Report 1991 (Box 194)
      - H.A.R.T. Properties, 2 folders (Box 194)
      - H.A.R.T. Properties, 1 folders (Box 195)
      - Hilltop -- Richmond Associates, 2 folders (Box 195)
      - Homart (Box 195)
      - International Society of Gastronomes, Correspondence 1990-1993 (Box 195)
      - Keewaydin Company (Box 195)
      - Kennedy (John F. Kennedy Library Foundation) 1997 (Box 195)
      - Kildee, Congressman Fundraiser at KW 1994 (Box 195)
      - King, Oscar 1986 (Box 195)
      - K-Mart
        - Maple & Livernois (Box 195)
        - Outer Sherwood (Box 195)
      - Knollenberg, Congressman Joe 1998 (Box 195)
      - Korab, Balthazar 1986-1987 (Box 195)
      - Mort Crim Communications 1996-1999 (Box 195)
      - Mount Vernon Ladies Association 1984-1987 Pledge (Box 195)
      - Novi Associates, 3 folders (Box 195)
      - Optima Fund Management 1995-2001 (Box 195)
      - Orioles, Baltimore 1975-1979 (potential purchase, with Max Fisher) (Box 196)
      - St. Andrew's Dune Church, Southampton, Jack Geary Memorial Fund 1995-1996 (Box 196)
      - 712 Fifth Avenue 1996-1998 (Box 196)
      - Spoleto Festival 1992-1995 (Box 196)
      - Sugar Babies Company Limited 1995-2000 (Box 196)
      - Taubman Company
        - Bylaws 1977 (Box 196)
        - Clippings
          - Miscellaneous 1985-1990 (Box 196)
          - Schools 1999 (Box 196)
          - Social 1985-1989 (Box 196)
          - Sotheby's 1983-1998 (Box 196)
          - Woodies 1984-1994 (Box 196)
        - Contributions, 2 folders (Box 196)
        - Correspondence 1975-1977 (Box 196)
        - D.C. Area Job Costs 1974 (Box 196)
        - Financial Statements 1974-1981 (Box 196)
        - Inquires 1977 (Box 196)
        - Inter-Departmental Meetings 1978-1979 (Box 196)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 196)
        - Public Relations 1977-1981 (Box 196)
      - Taubman Detroit 1978-1979 (Box 196)
      - Taubman Investments LLC, Report July 2003 (Box 196)
      - Taubman West Coast 1975-1980 (Box 196)
      - Taubman Realty Group
        - General 1976-1981 (Box 197)
        - Financial 1991-1992 (Box 197)
        - Partnership Handbook 1992 (Box 197)
      - Tiger Stadium 1991-1994, 14 folders (Box 197)
      - United Nations 50th Anniversary 1995 (Box 197)
      - World Cup Soccer 1994 (Box 197)
      - Yale University/Sid Bass 1986 (Box 197)
      - Young (Coleman Young Foundation) 1980-2003, 2 folders (Box 197)
    - A-D 1974-1985
      - A Miscellaneous (Box 198)
      - A & W
        - Activity Reports 1985 (Box 198)
        - Correspondence 1978-1985, 5 folders (Box 198)
        - Financial 1981-1985, 6 folders (Box 198)
        - Legal 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 198)
        - Legal 1984, 2 folders (Box 199)
        - Marketing Materials and Procedure Manual 1982-1985 (Box 199)
      - Alzheimer's 1984-1985 (Box 199)
      - American Associates of the Royal Academy Trust 1984 (Box 199)
      - American Friends of the Israel Museum 1981-1983 (Box 199)
      - American Hospital Foundation 1984-1985 (Box 199)
      - American Hospitality 1982-1983 (Box 199)
      - American Jewish Committee 1979-1983 (Box 199)
      - American Red Cross 1981-1985 (Box 199)
      - Anaheim Hills 1984 (Box 199)
      - Annabel's 1983-1984 (Box 199)
      - Architects 1962-1984 (Box 199)
      - Archives of American Art 1974-1985, 4 folders (Box 199)
      - Archives of American Art 1974-1985, 2 folders (Box 200)
      - Aronow, Adria 1980-1984 (Box 200)
      - A.R.T. Properties 1980-1984 (Box 200)
      - Art at Auction 1985 (Box 200)
      - Artists Space 1985-1986 (Box 200)
      - Asia Society 1984-1985 (Box 200)
      - B Miscellaneous 1984-1986 (Box 200)
        (includes letter from Sir Gordon Brunton)
      - Bellevue Associates 1981-1985 (Box 200)
      - Beloit College 1980-1984 (Box 200)
      - Bethlehem Steel 1967-1982 (Box 200)
      - Beverly Center/Hard Rock Café & Dance Centre 1982-1985 (Box 200)
      - Bloomfield Open Hunt Correspondence (Box 200)
      - Brandeis University (Box 200)
      - Brandywine Conservancy 1984 (Box 201)
      - Briarwood 1976-1985 (Box 201)
      - Brown, H.L., Jr. (Sonny) 1984 (Box 201)
      - C Miscellaneous 1980-1985 (Box 201)
      - Carimati Jewelers 1984 (Box 201)
      - Center Companies 1980 (Box 201)
      - Cleary College 1980-1983 (Box 201)
      - Cliff Hall Orchestra 1981 (Box 201)
      - Congregation Shaarey Zedek 1961-1976 (Box 201)
      - D Miscellaneous 1982-1984 (Box 201)
      - Dayton Hudson Correspondence 1980 (Box 201)
      - Detroit Grand Prix 1982-1985 (Box 201)
    - A, D 1979-1994
      - A Miscellaneous 1988-1991 (Box 202)
      - Ablah, George 1984, 1985 (Box 202)
      - American Agenda (Sandford Greenberg) 1989 (Box 202)
      - American Association of the Royal Academy Trust 1985-1994, 3 folders (Box 202)
      - American Friends of Israel Museum 1986, 1987, 1991, 1993 (Box 202)
      - American Friends of the Game Conservancy 1986 (Box 202)
      - American Museum at Bath 1986 (Box 202)
      - American Red Cross 1987 (Box 202)
      - American Spectator 1986-1991 (Box 202)
      - Anaheim Hills Festival with Pictures 1992 (Box 202)
      - Annabels 1989 (Box 202)
      - Archives of American Art 1983-1993, 3 folders (Box 202)
      - Art in the Stations (Detroit People Mover) (Box 202)
      - Arts Connection (Box 202)
      - Arts, Michigan Foundation for the Arts 1979-1988, 2 folders (Box 202)
      - The Asia Society 1986-1989, 2 folders (Box 203)
      - Atlantic Golf Club 1989-1994 (Box 203)
      - Auburn-Cord-Duesenberg Museum (Box 203)
      - D Miscellaneous 1987-1994 (Box 204)
      - de Fortabat, G-IV Negotiations (Box 204)
      - Detroit Club 1978-1992 (Box 204)
      - Detroit Free Press, 1988-1989 (Box 204)
      - Detroit Zoo, Chimpanzee Exhibit Pledge 1986-2001 (Box 204)
      - Development, Miscellaneous 1988-1989 (Box 205)
      - Bob Dole Presidential Campaign 1995-1996 (Box 205)
      - Bob Dole Presidential Campaign 1987-1988, 3 folders (Box 205)
      - Michele Oka Doner 1986 (Box 205)
      - Doubles International Club 1977-1994 (Box 205)
      - Harper-Grace Hospitals
        - Board of Trustees 1980-1988, 8 folders (Box 205)
        - MRI Center 1985-1987 (Box 205)
    - Miscellaneous 1960-1967
      - Brandeis University
        - Brandeis University Associates (Box 206)
        - Directories of Fellows (Box 206)
        - Eleanor Poplack Scholarship (Box 206)
      - Jewish Organizations
        - Allied Jewish Campaign (Box 206)
        - American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee (Box 206)
        - Detroit Friends of Yeshiva University (Box 206)
        - Detroit Service Group (Box 206)
        - Fred M. Butzel Memorial Building Management Committee (Box 206)
        - Jewish Community Center (Box 206)
        - Jewish Education (Box 206)
        - Jewish Welfare Federation
          - Board of Governors (Box 206)
          - Committee on Capital Needs (Box 206)
          - Delegate, General Assembly (Box 206)
          - Executive Committee (Box 206)
          - Special Literature (Box 206)
        - National Jewish Welfare Boards, workshops (Box 206)
        - United Hebrew Schools (Box 206)
        - United Jewish Appeal (Box 206)
      - Columbus City Center, 3 folders (Box 207)
      - Fairfax Partnership (Box 207)
      - Taubman Investment Company Board of Directors (Box 207)
      - Harper Grace Hospital (Box 207)
      - Government Studies (Box 207)
      - Founders Society of Detroit Institute of Art (Box 207)
      - Greater Detroit Chamber of Commerce (evaluation of the compact process) (Box 207)
      - Blenheim Foundation (Box 207)
      - Center for Creative Studies, 2 folders (Box 207)